I'm OK with both!
I'm ready to go calamine!
I'm ready to go!
I'm ready!
Oh, Haru, practice your pretty face!
Looking good!
I'm eating lunch now! And do you have anything else to drink?
Ah! I gotta go! That's what I'm talking about! I'm ready!
What am I going to do tomorrow?
I love it! I love it!
I don't know what to do about my hair.
Here's your haircut, day two.
Second day.
Grated and
Super high pony
It's a lie.
I have no hair.
I'm not sure what to do with my hair.
Conroe
Lack.
What do you mean, "Conroe"?
Dancers and such.
But it's for Mitsui.
It looks like a rack.
They made hearts here with Conroe.
So cute.
So I went to school.
Cecinon came to see me.
Here you go.
Here's the glue for the stain.
And here's the stain.
And this is the glue for the stain.
And this... and this...
This is the glue for stains
This is pigmentation glue.
What is this? What is this?
It says "complete the pudding.
It's an egg stain.
I've seen something like that before.
What do you mean?
I've seen pudding like that.
Great. I'll eat it when I'm done.
I'm down to four eggs.
I have five eggs.
But I sold four puddings in a case.
I'm sorry, I just have to put my name on it.
I want some pudding!
So this is the first time in a year that I'm going to be working with Tokisen Band.
We are TOKISEN BAND!
Yay!
We had a first time member last year, and this time we have a first time member too, but last year we were Yaon, weren't we?
Yaon last year.
It's been a year since we last met, so this time we're going to meet with a new band in a nice and beautiful arena.
I'm really, really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm so excited!
I have no choice but to go with all my heart and soul.
I'll be there!
I did it!
I'll do my best for the band, too.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'll do my best.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
I'll say it right away.
Let's do it by the way.
They're all gone.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! Great, great, great, great, great!
Let's go!
Kanin Junior!
HITOKO Maruko HITOKO Maruko
Aki Hiyori
Chik-chan
Chokotan Mizukinku
Okazu Remon
SENZEN PUN
LOCK ON
Yay!
congratulations!
best regards
Best regards
I look forward to working with you.
Pleasure to meet you
Rhythm, rhythm, rhythm, rhythm...
When you say your name...
When you say your name and your hand comes out like this.
When I get a little handsy.
Calamine, Julial.
They're all joking around, that guy, even his mouth, that cool kid...
It's an action, right?
Nice!
Cute!
Costume. It's a costume.
Cute, though,
Me too,
I thought you knew what I was talking about.
Don't film me.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't film me, I'm embarrassed.
This is the first venue for a female artist.
Well, we always start from our place.
Today,
Super Tokimeki Advertising Department, Tokimeki Haru no Hareebutai 2024.
I'm going to release the most crush in my history.
Thank you very much for coming to the Thank you very much for visiting us at
Oh, I made a mistake.
It's Hito-chan aka Osakai from Cho-Tokimeki-Retta
It's Akichan aka Osakai from Chotokimekiretta!
I tend to go to the opening of the show.
For the sake of your good wishes, I'd like to draw your attention to something.
The show will start soon!
It's been a while since we've performed even in Kyoto!
Today's show is going to rock!
We're going to rock!
Let's rock!
It's the Hamaband, ladies and gentlemen!
Are you ready to rock?
Let's make them think today was the most fun ever!
Let's do it!
Wait for us!
Oh, I'm not done yet.
I can't wait to see how you rank in the future.
Oh, no, no, no...
Hanami
Julia
Dutoko
Haruko
autumn
Hiyori
Then Tokimeki Advertising Department
Rock On
Goal
Aaaaah!
AHHHHH!
me
JR East E233 Series
East Japan Railway Series E233
Thank you for watching!
I can hear everyone's voice well. You've been all over the mountain. I can hear you all so well.
I hope you're all waiting for me.
I'm going to approach your seats now.
I'm wearing a cute T-shirt. Encore T-shirt, Toxen-arranged version.
It's on my badge.
I wonder if they'll notice.
I'll have to get a cute picture of me.
It's okay.
With Aki.
"Hihihi."
"Hihihi" with Akichan.
Here we go.
"Hee-hee-hee."
"Hihi-hihi!"
Thank you all for listening to my cue today.
I've been having so much fun that I've realized once again how fast time flies.
I felt it again today.
Did you have a good time too?
What was that? I forgot what I was going to say just now.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
We haven't seen each other for three months, right?
We haven't been able to see each other without saying so.
I was really cheered up by all the messages and comments from everyone.
I was really cheered up by your messages and comments.
But when we performed live again, I felt the power and excitement that you can only get at a live concert.
I was able to reconfirm that there is this power and excitement that you can only get at a live concert.
I was also able to recharge with a great deal of excitement.
I'm glad that we can continue to exchange these crushes together with you all.
I would be happy if we could exchange these crushes with each other.
I hope you all will continue to give me your crushes!
Thank you very much for today.
I'm really happy to see a full house today.
I was really happy to see a full house today.
It's April, which means that we're starting our new lives.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who have a lot of hard work ahead of them.
We hope we can give you a lot of energy and motivation through our live and social networking services.
I hope we can give you energy and motivation to do your best every day through our live performances and social networking.I would be happy if I could give you the feeling of doing your best every day.
The stage is long and wide.
Basically, everywhere I looked, everyone was there, and I felt very happy.
I felt so happy.
As Julia said, it's April.
people who are starting a new school life, people who got a new job, people who changed their jobs, etc.
People who started a new school, got a new job, changed jobs, etc.
I think everyone is going through various changes in their environment.
I'm sure there are times when you're going through hard times, or you're in pain, or you don't know what to do...
We are all the same, you know.
But at times like that, everyone is always there to be a light for us.
You are always there for us and for everyone else.
I hope we can be like a light for you.
I hope you will continue to follow us.
I hope you will follow us for a long time.
Thank you very much.
I think idols are wonderful.
I feel that it's wonderful to be an idol every day, or rather, to perform live to a full house.
It's not easy to continue being an idol
But there are people I've met because I've continued to be an idol.
Like Kurosawa-san mentioned earlier.
If I hadn't been an idol, or if I hadn't done TOKISEN...
It's because of each one of those opportunities
I would not have met the people I've met and the things I've been able to do
That's the kind of work that I can do.
I feel that being an idol is really wonderful every day.
I love idols myself.
I love idols myself, and I also love myself as an idol very, very much.
For those of you who said "I was so happy to hear you say you love me
I'm happy for you!
Maybe you've heard about us in the last 3 months and came to our live for the first time.
and came to our live for the first time.
For those who came for the first time
Yay!
Cho-Takimeki-Ten Debut is a band that performs and sings with all its might, anytime, anywhere.
No matter how far away, no matter how far in the corner, we're doing our best to deliver takimeki to you, our idols.
Good for you. I hope you like us more and more and more.
If you're free again, please come back tomorrow. Come back tomorrow if you're free.
During the opening movie, everyone cheered so loudly that we could hear it.
That made me so happy and I thought, "Oh my God, we're wanted here!
We could really feel it from their cheers and smiles on stage.
Thank you so much for always bringing us love.
Thank you so much.
The fact that we were able to perform at this kind of venue is one of the reasons.
And like I said before, being able to perform with Mr. Kurosawa, who I love so much.
and to have you write the lyrics for the song.
I think it's thanks to all of you that these things came true.
It's because of everyone's support that these things came true.
Thank you so much for always making our dreams come true.
Thank you very much.
"Oh!
Good job! Good!
"Good job on the guitar!"
Great!
Ladies and gentlemen, please sit down with yourselves.
Thank you.
You're the best.
Never fails.
Good work, sir.
Thanks for your hard work
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much
Yes, so, Day1 of Tokimeki Haru's big day is over.
Yay!
It's been a while since your last live performance, how was it?
I, when I'm moved, it's so beautiful, isn't it?
It's nice.
And it's like the first opening video.
It was amazing.
And then the red-black-yellow outfit was amazing, and the costumes look great on you.
Indeed. Indeed.
This was the first time I had shown it off.
It was totally different from the usual.
I was surprised.
It rocks so much.
This is cute.
It's super cute.
Super cute.
Everyone got a lot of energy.
I feel like we were energized, so now we have a chance to change for tomorrow.
Yes, let's do our best tomorrow.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
Maybe now we're going to try hard tomorrow.
I'm going to rock tomorrow, man.
What's wrong with your voice?
Maybe it's a variable phase.
I'm in a variable phase.
I think it's more of a change than mine.
But I'm okay with either one.
It's rock 'n' roll.
There are so many different voices.
Wait a minute.
Can you guys make it tomorrow?
I can do it.
We can do it.
Everybody, everybody.
I can't, I can't, I can't.
We can do it. We can do it.
We'll take our chances.
We, we, we.
We're gonna make it happen.
Come on, guys.
Can you make it tomorrow?
We can do it.
Yeah.Yay.
Yay.
I'm going to keep going like this tomorrow.
Hang in there.
I got courage.
Thank you for the day.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching
Let's go, Tumo Tumo Tumoro, the strongest theory of all.
Hello hello hello to the new you.
I don't care what they say
Let's go for it, let's go for it, let's go for it!
We're going to make the most powerful live show ever...
With the six of us, and the publicist...
With everyone's voice
I think it's the strongest live!
So I want to come back to this big, big Saitama Super Arena with all of you.
I want to come back to this big Saitama Super Arena with all of you.
It may be a big dream.
But if we all do our best to pursue our dreams together
I'm sure we can make it come true.
Let's make such a big dream come true together.
Let's become even more powerful members of the Tokimeki Advertising Department!
Thank you for watching!
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turned color
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
It leads me to the future.
Subtitle: KiminomiyaSubtitle Kiminomiya
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
When you're lost, just remember
So that I can smile even when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good-bye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
The town after the rain, the waves are shimmering
So my heart is clear
Someday I'll play the rainbow piano
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
The city after the rain, the waves are shimmering
So my heart is clear
Tears are filling me up
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Thank you for watching!